Why the application of our pastor for the first Christmas, especially all weeks?
Father, right now, let us think of someone in our community who's not at this meeting,
but who works for you and for us.
Father, we ask you to protect them, keep them safe,
and even each person in this room.
We ask you to do this at one age 24, and look forward to this next year.
I thank you for the ones here who make decisions, decisions that they know you will guide them in.
And even tonight, take care of them, bless them with stress.
They're under and let them just be able to think about what you want them to do.
Jesus name up for eight.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the five of the United States of America, and to the Republic of Japan.
One nation, a background and a digital, a digital, a digital, a digital...
For what? Well, again, I'm a good personal parent, so this is five.
Kind of list.
Oh, should we approve?
Second.
Is that?
Hi.
Farons?
I'm Jones.
Hi.
Six minutes from the December 2, 2024 regular meeting,
at a December 16th, 2020 four-regard me.
What's your favorite?
Second.
A step by.
Barnes, I. Jones, I.
Local.
Parker.
Guy.
Other new businesses of any of which the residents of the
Supposing this have been.
Eight staff reports.
Nine trustee community announcements.
Normally I'd wait till the second.
What we need to do that, but I'm going to do it now, so it's.
We've got.
Misty Barnes is now.
What this is our new city attorney.
So new face up here.
So we're welcoming you aboard.
And we also have Crystal White.
It's our CFO that's also not in here.
We're welcoming both of them aboard.
Thank you.
Dan.
This may not be redeemed from the.
Council chambers redeemed the staff room.
The purpose of executive session.
The completion of the regular meeting of the mile.
Industrial public facilities authority.